web2summit.com 2013-05-21

# Privacy Policy: Web 2.0 Summit 2011 - Co-produced by UBM TechWeb & O'Reilly Conferences, October 17 - 19, 2011, San Francisco

This policy discloses what information we gather about you when you visit any of our Web sites or buy product directly from us. It describes how we use that information and how you can control it. Our privacy policy addresses:

  * Information we gather and track
  * Personal information
  * Aggregated tracking information
  * Cookies
  * Third Party Cookies
  * Third Party Advertising
  * Notification of Changes
  * How to update, correct, or delete your information

### Information we gather and track

O'Reilly and TechWeb collect two kinds of information about users: 1) data that users volunteer by signing up to receive news and product information, entering contests, completing surveys, or buying directly from us; and 2) aggregated tracking data we collect when users interact with us. 

### Personal information

We use the personal information you provide voluntarily to send information you've requested and to fulfill orders. The specific use of your personal information varies, depending on how you contact us:

#### Signing up for email newsletters or conference/expo updates:

  * When you sign up online to receive Web 2.0 or Gov 2.0 Expo or Summit newsletters, you must provide your name and email address. We never sell or rent your email address or other personally identifiable information you provide us under these circumstances.
  * You will have the option to opt in to our third party list to receive relevant offers from our sponsors and partners. Sponsors and partners will then have the option to occasionally send you limited emails – we do not distribute or rent this list.
  * We will send you email announcements and updates about Web 2.0, Gov 2.0, and other O'Reilly and TechWeb products and services. We may send conference brochures to individuals who request information from us and provides a valid address.

#### Registering for a Web 2.0 or Gov 2.0 Expo or Summit event:

  * When you register for any Web 2.0 or Gov 2.0 Expo or Summit event we will send you email announcements and updates about Web 2.0, Gov 2.0, and other O'Reilly and TechWeb products and services. We may send conference brochures to past conference attendees. 
  * When you register for any Web 2.0 or Gov 2.0 Expo or Summit event, you have the option to opt in to our third party list to receive relevant offers from our sponsors and partners.
  * If you do not choose to opt-in to the third party list, your email address will not be shared with any party outside of TechWeb and O’Reilly.
  * We also may collect information about your professional responsibilities (such as job title, purchasing responsibilities, company information and professional certification). We use such information to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or for industry reporting purposes.
  * For our services that require payment (such as certain events, products and subscriptions), we also collect credit card information (such as account name, number and expiration date), which is used for our or our agent's billing purposes only, and is not otherwise shared.

We share customer information with affiliated companies (see <http://www.oreilly.com/affiliates.html>) and as described below:

  * With third parties we retain to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, managing mailing lists, and delivering packages. These parties are restricted from using your information for any other purpose.
  * We rent our snailmail list for one-time use to third parties we deem relevant and appropriate. We do not rent or sell our email lists.
  * We release personal information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of O'Reilly Media, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### Surveys and Contests

From time to time we invite web site users and other customers to provide information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. In addition to the other uses set forth in this policy, contact information collected in connection with surveys and contests is used to notify the winners and award prizes and to monitor or improve the use of, and satisfaction with the event, website or other TechWeb or O’Reilly product or service.

### Aggregated tracking information

We anonymously analyze visitors' use of our sites by tracking information such as pageviews, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites. We also share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form with advertisers and other business partners. We do not share any information with advertisers that can identify an individual user.

We use WebSideStory's Hitbox and Google Analytics, third party web analytics services to improve our web site performance and user experience. We use this information to improve usability on our sites and to help support our customers’ online needs. Hitbox and Google do not reveal any personally identifiable information, such as names or email address.

For more information on the Hitbox service and privacy policy, please see their privacy policy and privacy FAQ. Read the Google privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html "Opens link in a new browser window.").

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser when you visit our sites. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your computer, so that we can provide you with personalized information and features. We also use cookies to track user traffic patterns.

On our sites, we and some of our advertisers use a third-party ad server to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. The ad server receives these cookies, and we don't have access to them.

You can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies or to block cookies. If you block cookies, you may not be able to use certain site features or functions.

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to their site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please click here: <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>

### Notification of Changes

This privacy policy was put in effect on January 22, 2008.

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email. Users will be able to opt out of any new use of their personal information.

### How to update, correct, or delete your information

Email: To update or unsubscribe from our email newsletters or product announcements, change your address, delete your name from our mailing list (for paper catalogs or brochures) or to opt-out of third-party mail please send an email with your request to [web2unsub@techweb.com](mailto:web2unsub@techweb.com).
